Takayla Bush

3606 N 54th Blvd, Milwaukee, WI 53216, USA Milwaukee, WI, 53216 (414) 210-8772 bushtakaylab@yahoo.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Quality-oriented professional with 4.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of conflict resolution, customer needs assessment, and patient safety. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Certified Nursing assistant role at your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CALEDONI REHAB AND REHABILITATION, Caledonia, MN

Certified Nursing Assistant, Mar 2019 - Present

- Answer patient call signals, signal lights, bells, or intercom systems to determine patients' needs.
- Assist nurses in the operation of medical equipment or provision of patient care.
- Change bed linens or make beds.
- Clean and sanitize patient rooms, bathrooms, examination rooms, or other patient areas.
- Collect specimens, such as urine, feces, or sputum.
- Document or otherwise report observations of patient behavior, complaints, or physical symptoms to nurses.
- Feed patients or assist patients to eat or drink.
- Measure and record food and liquid intake or urinary and fecal output, reporting changes to medical or nursing staff.
- Observe or examine patients to detect symptoms that may require medical attention, such as bruises, open wounds, or blood in urine.
- Prepare or serve food travs.
- Record height or weight of patients.
- Record vital signs, such as temperature, blood pressure, pulse, or respiration rate, as directed by medical or nursing staff.
- Restock patient rooms with personal hygiene items, such as towels, washcloths, soap, or toilet paper.
- Supply, collect, or empty bedpans.
- Turn or reposition bedridden patients.
- Undress, wash, and dress patients who are unable to do so for themselves.
- Lift or assist others to lift patients to move them on or off beds, Assisting with all transfers

HARBOUR VILLAGE, Milwaukee, WI

Wi, Jun 2015 - Mar 2019

- Administer bedside or personal care, such as ambulation or personal hygiene assistance.
- Prepare and maintain records of client progress and services performed, reporting changes in client condition to manager or supervisor.
- Perform housekeeping duties, such as cooking, cleaning, washing clothes or dishes, or running errands.
- Care for individuals or families during periods of incapacitation, family disruption, or convalescence, providing companionship, personal care, or help in adjusting to new lifestyles.
- Perform healthcare-related tasks, such as monitoring vital signs and medication, under the direction of registered nurses or physiotherapists.
- Provide clients with communication assistance, typing their correspondence or obtaining information for them.
- Answer patient call signals, signal lights, bells, or intercom systems to determine patients' needs.
- Change bed linens or make beds.

ALTA RESOURCES, Milwaukee, WI

Customer service representative, Jun 2014 - Feb 2015

- Confer with customers by telephone or in person to provide information about products or services, take or enter orders, cancel accounts, or obtain details of complaints.
- Keep records of customer interactions or transactions, recording details of inquiries, complaints, or comments, as well as actions taken.
- Check to ensure that appropriate changes were made to resolve customers' problems.
- Refer unresolved customer grievances to designated departments for further investigation.
- Contact customers to respond to inquiries or to notify them of claim investigation results or any planned adjustments.
- Resolve customers' service or billing complaints by performing activities such as exchanging merchandise, refunding money, or adjusting bills.
- Solicit sales of new or additional services or products.

EDUCATION

Milwaukee area Technical College Milwaukee , WI Completed coursework towards D.N.P. Nursing (Nov 2015)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in microsoft excel software
- Scheduling experience

CREDENTIALS AND LICENSES

- Certified Nursing Assistant
- CBRF